### **CONTACT INFO**

#### **PHONE**

+506 8721 9070

#### **EMAIL**

carlos\_retana\_@outlook.com

#### **ADDRESS**

Desamparados, San José, Costa Rica

# **SKILLS**

- Web Development
- . Teamwork
- Responsible
- Passion for Al

# **LANGUAGES**

- Spanish native language
- English

#### **WEB RESUME**

carlos-retana.site

# CARLOS RETANA VIQUEZ

# **PROFILE**

I am currently studying systems engineering, I have also trained through courses where I have learned different methodologies. I have experience with CSS3, HTML5 and Javascript, I also have experience with libraries like React and Astro Build.

# **EDUCATION**

Ingeniería en Sistemas de Computación

2020 - Present

**Universidad Fidélitas** 

**Desarrollo Web** 

Apr 2022 - Dec 2022

**Alura Latam - ONE Oracle Next Education** 

Técnico en Diseño Gráfico

2015 - 2017

Tecnológico de Costa Rica

#### **EXPERIENCE**

ABC Design Diseñador Gráfico

2017 - 2019 Corporate identity and

logo design.

Technology used: Illustrator - Photoshop -

InDesign - XD

Vicar Médica Desarrollador Full Stack
Comercial Front-end and back-end

2022 - 2024 developer.

Technology used: JavaScript - HTML5 - CSS3